<resources>
    <string name="offer_data">Super Value Day: Save Up to Rs. 2400 as Amazon Pay Balance on
        your monthly shopping (ICICI Card Holders, 1st-3rd Mar)</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="about_us">Coupons App is a trusted brand and a pioneer in affiliate e-commerce
        scene in India. We are known for maintaining high quality standards through our unique user
        interface and user experience. We have been sustaining and preserving our USP, which is to
        provide the most authentic and updated coupons and deals. Today, Coupons App is the top player
        in the coupons and deals industry. But we aren’t new to media coverage, in fact the biggest
        news channels and newspapers in the country along with technological blogs have featured us
        on their platform. The likes of \'CNBC Awaaz\' have hailed us as Internet Heroes thus recognizing
        one of the most successful E-commerce affiliate start-ups from India.
            \n\tOur strategic B2B partnerships with some powerful e-commerce companies and strong network
        in the IT sector has benefited not only us but also our affiliates. Through our business
        partnership programs, we help a company increase its revenue, create brand awareness and
        expand its reach. Our network includes a wide range of merchants and strategic companies
        and our aim is to cross-promote each other in providing the best deals to the end-consumer.
        Coupons App receives partnership requests in bulk everyday but we intent to partner with
        businesses that offer our users just what they want from us. In the end it’s all about helping
        our users save on everything!</string>

    <string name="share_referral_main">Hey, I\'ve been using Coupons to get paid for my online shopping. they pay caashback for big online stores like flipkart, amazon, paytm and others. Its free to become a member and very easy to use. It\'s helped me save and you should try it too. Use my referral code to earn Rs.49 on your Sign Up. CODE: </string>
    <string name="share_referral">Hey, I\'ve been using Coupons to get paid for my online shopping. Sign Up through my referral code and earn Rs.49 on your registration. CODE: </string>

    <string name="app_name">Coupons</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="refer_data_main">Refer your friends and get 10% of their cashback \nearnings forever</string>
    <string name="refer_data">Refer your friends and earn Rs.49 on Sign Up</string>
    <string name="err_msg_email">Email is of wrong format</string>
    <string name="err_msg_required">Minimum of 6 charectors required</string>
    <string name="err_email_required">Invalid Email</string>
    <string name="err_msg_password">Password is of wrong format</string>
    <string name="auth_failed">Email or Password is invalid</string>

    <string name="facebook_app_id">430174674082628</string>
    <string name="fb_login_protocol_scheme">fb430174674082628</string>
</resources>
